Hi!
Before we start cleaning, it's always important to remove removable parts.
Generally, you don't want to keep your metal rack in your microwave unless you're using it.
It can cause problems with the microwave.
After we finish cleaning this, we're going to put it away instead of keeping it in our microwave.
Let's take this out.
Next, you're going to take out the glass tray, which enables everything to work on the turn table.
This definitely needs some cleaning.
We're going to clean that separately.
Another part is you have your turn table, the wheels.
You're going to remove this as well because for the most part, it's clean.
You've got it protected by the glass turn table most of the time, so you don't have to worry about this being cleaned.
You also don't want to use harsh chemicals on it.
Not that we're going to, but you just want to keep it as clean as possible.
We're going to remove it and set it to the side.
We have left our microwave.
You see we've got some crumbs on the inside here, so we're going to just kind of sweep those out while we get ready for our next step.